<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ryan Barkley</title><link>https://ryanbarkley.com/</link><description>Recent content on Ryan Barkley</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ryanbarkley.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://ryanbarkley.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ryanbarkley.com/about/</guid><description>Learning to make websites for fun Like many, I started making websites in my early teens—partially for fun and partially just to see if I could. I&amp;rsquo;d spend hours in Microsoft FrontPage (this was circa 2006, mind you) playing with the various wizards and GUI options, more than a little impressed with myself that I&amp;rsquo;d made a real website all on my own. Granted, it was very basic and would never see the light of the real world, but there was something about that small achievement that I found alluring.</description></item><item><title>Personal Digital Security</title><link>https://ryanbarkley.com/posts/personal-digital-security/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ryanbarkley.com/posts/personal-digital-security/</guid><description>While it is impossible to eliminate 100% of risk, there are a few (relatively) simple things you can do to reduce your risk in a meaningful way and help limit the blast radius if your password is compromised.</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>https://ryanbarkley.com/resources/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ryanbarkley.com/resources/</guid><description>Staying up-to-date Our industry is constantly changing, which can make it challenging to stay up-to-date on the latest trends and best practices. Below is a curated collection of some of my favorite industry resources I use to stay up-to-date aside from who I&amp;rsquo;m currently following on Twitter. (Following a bunch of smart people in the tech industry is one of the primary ways I passively stay up on the latest news and technologies.</description></item></channel></rss>